[♪♪♪]
♪ When your legs don't work
like they used to before ♪
♪ And I can't sweep you
off of your feet ♪
♪ Will your mouth still remember
the taste of my love ♪
♪ Will your eyes still smile
from your cheeks ♪
♪ Darlin, I will be lovin' you ♪
♪ Till we're seventy ♪
♪ And baby, my heart ♪
♪ Could still fall as hard
at 23 ♪
♪ And I'm thinking about how ♪
♪ People fall in love
in mysterious ways ♪
♪ Maybe just the touch
of a hand ♪
♪ Well, me, I fall in love
with you every single day ♪
♪ And I just wanna
tell you I am ♪
♪ So honey, now ♪
♪ Take me into
your lovin' arms ♪
♪ Kiss me under the light
of a thousand stars ♪
♪ Place your head on
my beating heart ♪
♪ I'm thinking out loud ♪
♪ Maybe we found love ♪
♪ Right where we are ♪
♪ When my hair's all but gone
and my memory fades ♪
♪ And the crowds don't
remember my name ♪
♪ When my hands don't play
the strings the same way ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ I know you will still
love me the same ♪
♪ Cos honey, your soul ♪
♪ Could never grow old ♪
♪ It's evergreen ♪
♪ And baby your smile's ♪
♪ Forever in my mind
and memory ♪
♪ I'm thinking about how ♪
♪ People fall in love
in mysterious ways ♪
♪ And maybe it's all
part of a plan ♪
♪ I'll just keep on making
the same mistakes ♪
♪ Hoping that you'll
understand ♪
♪ That baby, now ♪
♪ Take me into
your lovin' arms ♪
♪ Kiss me under the light
of a thousand stars ♪
♪ Place your head on
my beating heart ♪
♪ Thinking out loud ♪
♪ That maybe we found love ♪
♪ Right where we are ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ So baby, now ♪
♪ Take me into
your lovin' arms ♪
♪ Kiss me under the light
of a thousand stars ♪
♪ Oh darling ♪
♪ Place your head on
my beating heart ♪
♪ Thinking out loud ♪
♪ Maybe we found love ♪
♪ Right where we are ♪
♪ Baby, we found love ♪
♪ And we found love
right where we are ♪